var __reflect = (this && this.__reflect) || function (p, c, t) {
    p.__class__ = c, t ? t.push(c) : t = [c], p.__types__ = p.__types__ ? t.concat(p.__types__) : t;
};
var QuestionCfg = (function () {
    function QuestionCfg() {
    }
    QuestionCfg.cfgs = {
        1: [
            {
                question: "It was the forerunner of the second industrial revolution，He was also the initiator of the Second World War。“it”Refer to？",
                selection: ["Britain", "Germany", "Japan", "U.S.A"],
                correct: 1
            },
            {
                question: "The event that pushed the appeasement policy to the top was？",
                selection: ["Germany's annexation of Austria", "Pearl Harbour ", "Conniving Germany to attack Poland", "Munich plot"],
                correct: 3
            },
            {
                question: "70Years ago6month，Germany launched a surprise attack on the Soviet Union，The expansion of World War II，12month，The scale of the war is further expanded，Its logo is？",
                selection: ["Moscow defense", "Pearl Harbour ", "Battle of Stalingrad", "Normandy landing"],
                correct: 1
            },
            {
                question: "In the Second World War，The symbol of the formation of the world anti fascist alliance is？",
                selection: ["Cairo Conference", "《United Nations country declaration》Publish", "Victory of Stalingrad's defense war", "The Pacific War broke out"],
                correct: 1
            },
            {
                question: "The mark of the opening of the second battlefield in Europe is？",
                selection: ["Attack on Pearl Harbor", "Battle of Moscow", "Conquering Berlin", "Normandy landing"],
                correct: 3
            },
            {
                question: "1991year，Reunification of Germany；The breakup of Germany before reunification was caused by that meeting？",
                selection: ["Paris Peace Conference", "Washington Conference", "Tehran Conference", "Yalta Conference"],
                correct: 3
            }
        ],
        2: [
            {
                question: "The first time in Japanese history“nucleus”blast，It appears in？",
                selection: ["1942year", "1943year", "1944year", "1945year"],
                correct: 3
            },
            {
                question: "Which country is Hitler's leader？",
                selection: ["U.S.A", "Germany", "China", "Japan"],
                correct: 1
            },
            {
                question: "stay1938year9After Munich conference at the end of the month，Churchill said：Let you choose between war and Disgrace，You chose shame，And you have to fight in the future。What Churchill said“you”Refer to？",
                selection: ["Chamberlain", "Daladier", "Hitler", "Mussolini"],
                correct: 0
            },
            {
                question: "Using Hitler to balance Stalin、The conspiracy to sacrifice Czechoslovakia in exchange for the flood of evil？",
                selection: ["Paris Peace Conference", "Washington Conference", "Munich Conference", "Yalta Conference"],
                correct: 2
            },
            {
                question: "The mark of the biggest scale of the second world war is？",
                selection: ["German raids on Poland", "The outbreak of the Soviet German war", "The outbreak of the Pacific War", "United Nations Declaration issued"],
                correct: 2
            },
            {
                question: "The international conference that decided to establish the United Nations was？",
                selection: ["Paris Peace Conference", "Washington Conference", "Yalta Conference", "General assembly of the United Nations"],
                correct: 2
            }
        ],
        3: [
            {
                question: "Where was the battle at the turning point of the Second World War？",
                selection: ["Moscow", "Normandy", "Berlin", "Stalingrad"],
                correct: 3
            },
            {
                question: "What kind of people does Hitler hate",
                selection: ["American", "Chinese", "Israel", "Japanese"],
                correct: 2
            },
            {
                question: "The time of Japan's defeat was？",
                selection: ["1945", "1950", "1955", "1948"],
                correct: 0
            },
            {
                question: "Japan and its alliance in World War II?",
                selection: ["U.S.A", "Germany", "China", "India"],
                correct: 1
            },
            {
                question: "The time of Hitler's death was？",
                selection: ["1948", "1950", "1945", "1944"],
                correct: 2
            },
            {
                question: "The international conference that decided to establish the United Nations was？",
                selection: ["Paris Peace Conference", "Washington Conference", "Yalta Conference", "General assembly of the United Nations"],
                correct: 2
            }
        ]
    };
    return QuestionCfg;
}());
__reflect(QuestionCfg.prototype, "QuestionCfg");
//# sourceMappingURL=QuestionCfg.js.map